A Guide to the Records of the Organized Women Voters of Arlington County, 1923-2015
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Records of the Organized Women Voters of Arlington County, 1923-2015
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
RG 17
27 boxes.
The Organized Women Voters of Arlington
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Arlington Historical Society and Nancy Renfro.
Custodial History
These records were collected by one of the members of the Organized Women Voters and donated to the Arlington County Historical Society. The group was donated to the Library as part of a larger donation from the Arlington Historical Society. Further donations were made by Nancy Renfro.
Historical Information
The Organized Women Voters of Arlington County was founded in 1923 as the Arlington County League of Women Voters, and later that same year changed its name to the Organized Women Voters in order to remain clearly independent of the now nationally known League of Women Voters. As of 2017, the organization was still active in Arlington County.
The objectives of the organization were "to collect and disseminate political and civic information; to be non partisan; and to be free to take action on any County problem." The Organized Women Voters has been active in educating Arlington County voters on voting procedures and political candidates, as well as actively supporting women candidates for County Board positions. The organization also sponsored two yearly local events for a number of years -- the Woman of the Year Award and the annual Birthday Luncheon.
Scope and Content
Record Group 17 houses the scattered records of the Organized Women Voters of Arlington County. The collection measures 9.2 linear feet, and ranges from 1923 to 2015. Found in this group are scattered meeting minutes, membership lists, meeting announcements, by laws and constitution, financial documentation, memorabilia, and newsclippings. Of particular interest are the early meeting minutes and correspondence for the 1923 through 1925 period. The collection also houses several photographs of members at their various functions.
Series 18 and 19 are binders put together by Nancy Renfro and Mimi Simms as a sort of yearbook for the club. These contain meeting agendas, minutes, Treasurer's Reports, correspondence (usually related to organizing OWV meetings and special events), and published material that supported meeting speakers. Some binders contained materials for multiple years, and cover the 1960s through the 1990s.
Series 20 are materials collected and organized by longtime member Nancy Renfro, and contain meeting minutes, correspondence, and published material documenting the OWV's activities from the 1990s through 2015. There are committee reports, supporting material for invited meeting speakers, membership directories, OWV's constitution and bylaws, and detailed reports on larger events such as Candidate's Night.
Series 21 are materials created and collected by Sue Renfro, Nancy's mother and another longtime member of OWV. This series mostly deals with issues surrounding school integration and public housing, but also touches on other school issues such as appointment of School Board members and school curriculum and a Virginia state sales tax. There are clippings, drafts of speeches and correspondence, meeting minutes and other published material with notations made by Mrs. Renfro, and occasional personal papers scattered throughout. Series 20 and especially Series 21 show conservative viewpoints to local, state, and national issues, and contain published materials that support these viewpoints.
Arrangement
Record Group 17 is arranged into series by either type of material or organizational event. Most of the series are incomplete and scattered.
Series 18 and 19 are organized chronologically by binder. Series 20 is organized by binder; the creator, Nancy Renfro, placed selected materials in plastic sleeves (some labeled), so each folder is the contents of one sleeve. Series 21, Sue Renfro's materials, were originally filed in several accordion folders, many of which were labeled, and with some smaller mailing envelopes inside. Each subseries reflects one of those accordion folders, and Renfro's titles of the larger folders or mailing envelopes are in quotes [""]. The last subseries contains the smaller accordion folders.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Women in community organization; Women -- United States -- Societies and clubs.; Voting -- United States.; Arlington (Va.); Arlington County (Va.)
Contents List
- Biographies of Members
  - A (Box 1)
  - B (Box 1)
  - C-D (Box 1)
  - E-F (Box 1)
  - G-H (Box 1)
  - J-L (Box 1)
  - M (Box 1)
  - N-P (Box 1)
  - R (Box 1)
  - S-Z (Box 1)
  - "Short Bios of Various Members" (Box 1)
- Birthday Luncheon
  - Awards (Box 1)
  - Background on speakers (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1982 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1991 (Box 1)
  - Invitations (Box 1)
  - Press Releases, 1961-1987 (incomplete) (Box 1)
  - Programs, 1949, 1966, 1973-1982 (Box 1)
  - Programs, 1983-1991 (Box 2)
  - Reservation Lists, 1973-1984 (Box 2)
  - Reservation Lists, 1987-1991, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Supporting documents (Box 2)
- By-laws and Constitutions
  - Original drafts (Box 2)
  - 1928-1939 (Box 2)
  - 1945 (Box 2)
  - 1950s (Box 2)
  - 1960s (Box 2)
  - 1970s (Box 2)
  - 1980s (Box 2)
  - Not dated (Box 2)
- Correspondence Note: There is correspondence in Subgroup 14: Records (office)
  - 1925-1927 (Box 2)
  - 1928-1929 (Box 2)
  - 1930 (Box 2)
  - 1931 (Box 2)
  - 1932 (Box 2)
  - 1933 (Box 2)
  - 1934 (Box 3)
  - 1935 (Box 3)
  - 1936 (Box 3)
  - 1937 (Box 3)
  - 1938 (Box 3)
  - 1939 (Box 3)
  - 1940 (Box 3)
  - 1941 (Box 3)
  - 1945 (Box 3)
  - 1946 (Box 3)
  - 1947 (Box 3)
  - 1950 (Box 3)
  - 1951 (Box 3)
  - 1952 (Box 3)
  - 1953 (Box 3)
  - 1954 (Box 3)
  - 1955 (Box 4)
  - 1956 (Box 4)
  - 1957 (Box 4)
  - 1958 (Box 4)
  - 1959 (Box 4)
  - 1960 (Box 4)
  - 1961 (Box 4)
  - 1962 (Box 4)
  - 1963 (Box 4)
  - 1964 (Box 4)
  - 1965 (Box 4)
  - 1967 (Box 4)
  - 1968 (Box 4)
  - 1969 (Box 4)
  - 1970 (Box 4)
  - 1977 (Box 4)
  - 1978 (Box 4)
  - 1979 (Box 4)
  - 1980 (Box 4)
  - 1981 (Box 4)
  - 1982 (Box 4)
  - 1983 (Box 4)
  - 1984 (Box 4)
  - 1985 (Box 4)
  - 1987 (Box 4)
  - 1988 (Box 4)
  - 1989 (Box 4)
  - 1990 (Box 4)
  - 1991 (Box 4)
  - List of correspondents, 1973-1985 (Box 4)
  - Personal correspondence to Sue Renfro, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Not dated (Box 4)
- Financial
  - Bankbooks, bank statements, cancelled checks
    - 1928-1969 (incomplete) (Box 5)
    - 1923-1941 (Box 5)
    - 1942-1949, 1953 (Box 5)
    - 1954 (Box 5)
    - 1955 (Box 5)
    - 1956 (Box 5)
    - 1957 (Box 5)
    - 1958 (Box 5)
    - 1959 (Box 5)
    - 1960 (Box 5)
    - 1961 (Box 5)
    - 1962 (Box 5)
    - 1963 (Box 5)
    - 1964 (Box 5)
    - 1965 (Box 5)
    - 1966 (Box 5)
    - 1967 (Box 5)
    - 1968 (Box 5)
    - 1969 (Box 5)
    - 1971 (Box 6)
    - 1972 (Box 6)
    - 1974 (Box 6)
    - 1976 (Box 6)
    - 1977 (Box 6)
    - 1978 (Box 6)
    - 1979 (Box 6)
    - Cancelled checks, 1940-1953, 1974 (incomplete) (Box 6)
  - Check Stubs
    - 1934-1953 (Box 6)
    - 1954-1962 (Box 6)
    - 1964-1970 (Box 6)
    - Bank check records 1961-1968, 1970-1974, and cashbook, 1954-1963 (Box 6)
  - Returned Checks
    - 1936-1941 (Box 6)
    - 1926-1941 (Box 7)
    - 1951, 1956-1963 (Box 7)
    - 1964-1969 (Box 7)
    - 1970-1978 (Box 7)
    - 1974-1978 (Box 7)
    - 1979-1980, n.d. (Box 7)
  - Returned Checks
    - 1936-1941 (Box 7)
    - 1926-1941 (Box 7)
    - 1951, 1956-1963 (Box 7)
    - 1964-1969 (Box 7)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 7)
    - 1974-1978 (Box 7)
    - 1979-1980, n.d. (Box 7)
  - Reports
    - Auditor's reports, 1960-1979 (Box 7)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1945-1962 (Box 7)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1958-1977 (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1962-1969 (Box 7)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1972-1978 and DAR, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
  - Notebooks
    - Tax revenue notebooks, 1958-1959 (Box 8)
    - Programs, timetables, log type lists, 1960, 1986, n.d. (Box 8)
- Legal
  - Hendrick case, re: Waycroft Subdivision, Ruby Simpson, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Arlington Investment Corporation, Ruby Simpson, 1931-1935 (Box 8)
  - Legal citations (Box 8)
- Membership
  - Applications, 1976-1983 (Box 8)
  - Lists of members, 1931-1939 (Box 8)
  - Lists of members, 1940s-1950s (Box 8)
  - Lists of members, 1960s (Box 8)
  - List of members, 1970s (Box 8)
  - List of members, 1977-1979 (Box 8)
  - LIst of members, 1980s (Box 8)
  - Lists of members, 1980s (Box 9)
  - Directories, 1982-1986 (Box 9)
  - Directories, 1982-1986 (Box 9)
  - Directories, 1990s (Box 9)
  - Not dated (Box 9)
- Minutes of Meetings
  - Announcements and Meeting Notices
    - Announcements, 1960-1991 (Box 9)
    - Notices, 1969-1989 (Box 9)
  - Committee Minutes
    - General, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
    - Budget, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Civic, 1929, 1930, 1939, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1978 (Box 9)
    - County Government, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Education, 1924 (Box 9)
    - Education, 1967-1969 (Box 9)
    - Federal, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - Hospital, n.d. (Box 9)
    - Legislative, 1935, 1939 (Box 9)
    - Membership, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
    - Nominating, 1931-1986 (incomplete) (Box 9)
    - State and County Government, 1939-1940, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Sunshine, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Tax and revenue, 1958, 1960, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Executive Meeting Minutes
    - 1925-1927 (Box 10)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 10)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 10)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 10)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 10)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 10)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - 1944 (Box 10)
    - 1945 (Box 10)
    - 1946 (Box 10)
    - 1947 (Box 10)
    - 1950-1953 (Box 10)
    - 1954 (Box 10)
    - 1955 (Box 10)
    - 1950-1953 (Box 10)
    - 1957 (Box 10)
    - 1958 (Box 10)
    - 1959 (Box 10)
    - 1960 (Box 10)
    - 1961-1965 (Box 10)
    - 1961 (Box 10)
    - 1963 (Box 10)
    - 1964 (Box 10)
    - 1966 (Box 10)
    - 1967 (Box 10)
    - 1968 (Box 10)
    - 1969 (Box 10)
    - 1970 (Box 10)
    - 1975 (Box 10)
    - 1976 (Box 10)
    - 1977 (Box 10)
    - 1978 (Box 10)
    - 1979 (Box 10)
    - 1980 (Box 10)
    - 1981 (Box 10)
    - 1982 (Box 10)
    - 1983 (Box 10)
    - 1984 (Box 10)
    - 1986 (Box 10)
    - 1987 (Box 10)
    - 1988 (Box 10)
    - 1989 (Box 10)
    - 1990 (Box 10)
    - Not dated (Box 10)
  - General meeting minutes
    - Charter Meeting and Membership List 1923 (Box 10)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 10)
    - 1929 (Box 10)
    - 1930 (Box 11)
    - 1931 (Box 11)
    - 1932 (Box 11)
    - 1933 (Box 11)
    - 1934 (Box 11)
    - 1935 (Box 11)
    - 1936 (Box 11)
    - 1937 (Box 11)
    - 1938 (Box 11)
    - 1939 (Box 11)
    - 1940 (Box 11)
    - 1941 (Box 11)
    - 1943 (Box 11)
    - 1945 (Box 11)
    - 1946 (Box 11)
    - 1947 (Box 11)
    - 1949 (Box 11)
    - 1950 (Box 11)
    - 1951 (Box 11)
    - 1952 (Box 11)
    - 1953 (Box 11)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 11)
    - 1956 (Box 11)
    - 1957 (Box 11)
    - 1958 (Box 11)
    - 1959 (Box 11)
    - 1960 (Box 11)
    - 1961 (Box 11)
    - 1962 (Box 11)
    - 1963 (Box 11)
    - 1964 (Box 11)
    - 1965 (Box 11)
    - 1966 (Box 11)
    - 1967 (Box 11)
    - 1968 (Box 11)
    - 1969 (Box 11)
    - 1970 (Box 11)
    - 1975 (Box 11)
    - 1976 (Box 11)
    - 1977 (Box 11)
    - 1978 (Box 11)
    - 1979 (Box 11)
    - 1980 (Box 11)
    - 1981 (Box 11)
    - 1982 (Box 11)
    - 1983 (Box 11)
    - 1984 (Box 11)
    - 1986 (Box 11)
    - 1987 (Box 11)
    - 1988 (Box 11)
    - 1989 (Box 11)
    - 1990 (Box 11)
    - 1991 (Box 11)
  - Summary of minutes
    - Summary of minutes 1934-1938 and 1950-1958 (Box 11)
- Newsletters
  - 1963, 1982, 1984 (Box 11)
- Newspaper Clippings
  - 1929-1990, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Juvenile Jail, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Schools, 1957, 1959 (Box 11)
- Organization and Clubs
  - Arlington County Civic Federation, 1935-1991 (incomplete) (Box 13)
  - Arlington County Government, 1957-1983 (incomplete) (Box 13)
  - County Manager Newsletter, October 1960 - July 1961 (Box 13)
  - Federation of Homemakers and housing material, 1962, 1965, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Neighborhood civic associations, 1950-1984 (incomplete) (Box 13)
  - Schools (Box 13)
  - Speaker's bureau, 1980s (Box 13)
  - Numerous clubs A-M (Box 13)
  - Numerous clubs N-W (Box 13)
- Photographs and Slides
  - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Slides (Box 13)
- Politics
  - Candidate brochures (Box 13)
  - Candidate correspondence, 1981-1989 (incomplete) (Box 13)
  - Candidate questionnaire, 1959, 1976, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Election, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Legislative packages, 1985-1988 (Box 14)
  - Legislative issues, 1961, 1976-1989 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - National politics (Box 14)
- Records (office)
  - 1923-1930s (Box 14)
  - 1940s (Box 14)
  - 1950s (Box 14)
  - 1960s (Box 14)
  - 1970s (Box 14)
  - 1980s (Box 14)
  - 1990s (Box 14)
  - Not dated (Box 14)
- Resolutions
  - 1920s (Box 14)
  - 1930s (Box 14)
  - 1940s (Box 14)
  - 1950s (Box 14)
  - 1960s (Box 14)
  - 1970s (Box 14)
  - 1980s (Box 14)
  - 1990s (Box 14)
  - 1982 (Box 14)
  - 1983 (Box 14)
  - 1984 (Box 14)
  - 1986 (Box 14)
  - 1987 (Box 14)
  - Not dated (Box 14)
- Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbook, 1941-1988 (Box 15)
  - Scrapbook, 1935-1961 (Box 15)
  - 1970s Scrapbook, 1970-1974, n.d. (Box 15)
- Subjects
  - Aging, 1959-1962 (Box 16)
  - Agriculture foreign investment, 1978 (Box 16)
  - American Farm Land Trust (Box 16)
  - Arlington County board meetings (Box 16)
  - Arlington County budgets, 1963-1984 (Box 16)
  - Arlington County - County manager form of government (Box 16)
  - Arlington County Ad HOc Advisory Committee on Alternative Services Delivery System, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - Arlington County Jail, 1930 (Box 16)
  - Birthday party for U.S. Senator Harry Byrd Jr., 1982 (Box 16)
  - 3 x 5 cards with gifts and costs with names (Box 16)
  - Civil Rights, 1957-1960 (Box 17)
  - Civil Rights, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Civil Rights, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Civil Rights, 1980s (Box 17)
  - Commission on Aging, 1983-1984 (Box 17)
  - Daycare Center, 1978-1980 (Box 17)
  - Drug smuggling (Box 17)
  - Education, 1930-1977, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO) (Box 17)
  - Foreign affairs El Salvador and Nicaragua (Box 18)
  - Health, 1962-1977 (Box 18)
  - Histories, 1923-1983 (incomplete) (Box 18)
  - Housing, 1982-1984 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Obituaries, 1954-1989, n.d. (incomplete) (Box 18)
  - Panama Canal, 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Playgrounds report (Box 18)
  - Police and fire department pension system (Box 18)
  - Report on clean-up campaign in Arlington County particularly the Negro settlment in Queen City and East Arlington, 1937-1938 (Box 18)
  - Senior citizens, 1976-1984 (Box 18)
  - Sheriff's office (Box 18)
  - Sketches written and performed at the first annual meeting (Box 19)
  - Solicitations from organizations (for money) (Box 19)
  - Television (Box 19)
- Nancy Renfro Notebooks
  - Binder 1
    - "Renfro Papers 1935," 1935 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers 1960," 1960 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers OWV 1967," 1965-1967 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers OWV 1972-1973," 1928, 1972 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers OWV 1976," 1976 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers OWV 1977," 1977 (Box 19)
  - Binder 2
    - "OWV May 14, 1974 - May 23, 1978 (1)" (Box 19)
    - "OWV May 14, 1974 - May 23, 1978 (2)" (Box 19)
  - 1977-1979 Binder
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979," 1962, 1967, 1968, 1975, 1976 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979," 1967, n.d. (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979," 56th Anniversary Booklet, 1979 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979: 1978 ERA," 1978 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979: no info or date - 1968?", n.d. (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979: 1978-1979," 1974, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979: 1978," 1978, 1990 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979: 1977," 1977 (Box 19)
    - "Renfro Papers, 1977-1979," 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 19)
- Lillian "Mimi" Simms Notebooks
  - "Simms Papers 1950s-1980s, Book I," 1956, 1958, 1962, n.d. (Box 19)
  - "Simms Papers 1950s-1980s, Book II," 1970-1979, 1982-1984, 1989, 1991 (Box 19)
  - "Simms Papers 1989-1999," 1988-1999 (Box 19)
- Administrative Binders
  - "O.W.V., 8/93-5/98," 1993-1998 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 9/1998-5/1999," 1998-1999 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 9/1999-5/2000," 1999-2000 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 9/2000-5/2001," 2000-2001 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 9/2001 to 5/2002," 2001-2002 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 2002-2003," 2002-2003 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 2003-2004, 2004-2005," 2002-2005 (Box 19)
  - "Organized Woen Voters, 2005-2006, 2006-2007," 2005-2007 (Box 19)
  - "Organized Women Voters, 2007-2008," 2007-2008 (Box 19)
  - "OWV June 2008 to May 2009," 2008-2009 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 2009-2010," 2009-2010 (Box 19)
  - "OWV 2011-2013," 2011-2013 (1)* (Box 19)
  - "OWV 2011-2013," 2011-2013 (2) (Box 19)
  - "Organized Women Voters of Arlington, June 2013-May 2015," 2013-2015* (Box 19)
- Sue Renfro Records
  - "2nd Vice President" Folder
    - OWV Board Activities, 1961 (Box 19)
    - Speaker Invitations, 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - County Board Dealings, 1958, 1961 (Box 19)
    - Drafts of Public Statements, 1957, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Arlington Public Schools Personnel Policies and Salaries, 1953, 1955, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Building Yorktown High School, 1958, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Schools (general), 1943, 1953-1956, n.d. (Box 19)
    - "Speech by Father Edmond A. Walsh," 1952, n.d.* (Box 19)
    - OWV Stationary and Envelopes (Box 19)
    - Personal Correspondence and Forms, 1940-1944, 1960-1961* (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961, n.d. (Box 19)
  - "School Tuition Grants" Folder
    - Tax and Revenue Committee, 1958, 1959, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Legislative Committee, 1959 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1959, n.d. (Box 19)
    - OWV Proclamations, 1959, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Notes and Drafts, 1958, n.d. (Box 19)
    - School Segregation Strategies, 1959, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 19)
    - "Organized Women Voters Constitution and Bylaws," September 1958 (Box 19)
    - Arlington County Civic Federation (Box 19)
    - Campaign Literature, 1958, n.d. (Box 19)
    - State and Federal Regulations, 1959 (Box 19)
    - Congressional Record, 1959 (Box 19)
  - "Redevelopment 1958 Tax and Revenue Committee" Folder
    - Working Papers, 1958 (1) (Box 19)
    - Working Papers, 1950 (2) (Box 19)
    - Federal Publications, 1957, 1958, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Published Material, 1958 (Box 19)
    - County Board Minutes, 1958 (Box 19)
    - Clippings, 1953, 1954, 1957, 1958 (Box 19)
    - Personal Materials, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Public Housing Folder
    - Material on Public Housing, National Association of Real Estate Boards, 1958 (Box 19)
    - Articles on Segregation and Public Housing, 1954-1957, n.d. (Box 19)
    - "Public Housing in New York City," 1957 (Box 19)
    - "Report on the Need to Establish a Housing and Redevelopment Authority, by Tax and Revenue Committee, OWV," October 28, 1958 (Box 19)
    - "Public Housing Fact Book," 1958 (Box 19)
  - Unnamed Folder
    - "From Senate Document Room, HR 696," 1959 (Box 19)
    - State Sales Tax, 1960 (Box 19)
    - School Board Appointments, 1959 (Box 19)
    - County Board and Planning, 1958 (Box 19)
    - Clippings and Publications, 1959-1960 (Box 19)
    - Personal Papers, 1958-1959, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Smaller Folders
    - "Resolution for Public Hearing on School Board Nominations," 1957 (Box 19)
    - "Election Data on Redevelopment and Housing," 1958 (Box 19)
    - "Miscellaneous News Clippings," 1957-1962 (Box 19)
    - Yearbooks, 1984, 1990-1993, n.d. (Box 19)
- Audio Cassette Box 1
  - January 22, 1980, Martin Brown changes in Income Tax
  - August 13, 1980
  - August 13, 1980, Vietnam Remembered
  - September 1980
  - September 1981, House of Delegates Race
  - Fall 1981, Col. Harrington
- Audio Casseette Box 2
  - February 23, 1982, Dr. Martin Wasserman
  - March 5, 1982, Exec. Committee re: Constitutin and By-laws (2 tapes)
  - March 23, 1982, County Manager Griffin
  - April 27, 1982, Senatory Byrd's birthday (2 tapes)
- Audio Cassette Box 3
  - September 1983, Candidates County Board and committee officers
  - April 1984, VEPC Walter Frankland guest representing Chamber of Commerce (the other side is dated February 27, 1979
  - May 22, 1984, 63rd Birthday
  - October 25, 1983, Candidate meeting Warren Stambaugh
- Audio Cassette Box 4
  - April 28, 1987
  - May 4, 1987, Birthday
  - May 8, 1987, Secore/Coulter/Jenkins (Ga.)/McCollum R. (Fla.) Green (3 tapes)
  - May 11, 1987, McFarlane
  - May 11, 1987
- Audio Cassette Box 5
  - May 11, 1987, McFarlane (2 tapes)
  - May 12, 1987 (2 tapes)
  - May 13, 1987, McFarlane, Nunn, Rodino
- Audio Cassette Box 6
  - May 14, 1987, McFarlane, Sigur
  - May 14, 1987, Sigur
  - May 14, 1987, Sigur (2 tapes)
  - May 15, 1987
  - January 23, 1990
- Audio Cassette Box 7
  - March 27, 1990
  - April 2, 1990
  - May 21, 1991
  - March 24, 1992, Helen E. Fahey Commonwealth
  - March 24, 1992
  - March 23, no year Act. County Manager Griffin guest speaker
- Artifact Box
  - This material was the party favors that were given as souvenires at the Birthday Luncheons. The material includes pens, key chains, and potholders.